var sectiondata = {"sectiontag":"S","sectionname":"Prenatal Service Usage","qcount":10,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Please tell me about the public services you have used in the past 4 weeks. I\r\nhave a list of services that I'll go through to help jog your memory.\r\nPlease let me know if you have accessed the service, or are waiting to\r\naccess the service.\r","id":"q1","qnum":"q1"},"2":{"question":"Financial Assistance\r","id":"q2","qnum":"q2","acount":9,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Income Assistance (includes Disability, Hardship)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Employment Insurance and Maternity Benefits","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Special refundable tax rebates (GST\/HST rebates)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Medical Services Premium Assistance","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Rental Assistance","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Adult Basic Education (ABE) Student Assistance Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a6-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q1","id":"q2-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a6-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}At Home Respite Benefits","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a7-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q1","id":"q2-a7-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a7-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a7-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a7-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a7-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a7-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a7-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"8":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Non-Insured Health Benefits Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a8-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q1","id":"q2-a8-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a8-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q1","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q3","id":"q2-a8-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q1","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q3","id":"q2-a8-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q1","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q3","id":"q2-a8-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q1","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q3","id":"q2-a8-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q1","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q2","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q3","id":"q2-a8-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"9":{"qnum":"q2","id":"q2","answer":"{#}Other financial benefits","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q2-a9-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q1","id":"q2-a9-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q2-a9-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q2","id":"q2-a9-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q2-a9-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q1","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q2","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q1","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q2","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q1","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q2","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q1","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q2","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q1","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q2","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q3","id":"q2-a9-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"question":"Pregnancy Related Programs\r","id":"PREG","qnum":"q3","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Pregnancy Outreach Program (Includes CPNP, POPs, Healthiest Babies Possible)","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Have you accessed or tried to access this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1","acount":3,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1","answer":"[1] I have accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a1-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1","answer":"[2] I have not accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Did you try to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you tried to access this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Please indicate the types of barriers that prevented you from accessing\r\nthis service? (If more than one, please list all)\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{1} Service not offered at a convenient time (e.g., during ?business? hours only)"},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{2} Service not offered at a convenient location (e.g., across town or out of town)"},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{3} Did not have the resources to travel to the service (e.g., no bus or taxi fare)"},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{4} Found the other costs to get there too high (e.g. time off work\/school)"},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{5} Health problems interfered (e.g. physical or mental health problems including substances)"},"6":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{6} Family problems interfered (e.g. unstable living situation, intimate partner violence)"},"7":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{7} Service not available (e.g., after hours primary healthcare)"},"8":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{8} Other ____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] No","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Please indicate what prevented you from trying to access this service:\r","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Perceived service as unnecessary (e.g., believed the service was not needed)"},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] Perceived service as ineffective (e.g., believed the service did not help)"},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[3] Perceived service as insensitive (e.g., culturally inappropriate)"},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[4] Was ashamed\/embarrassed to seek service (e.g., stigma associated with mental health\/substances)"},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[5] Perceived service as hostile (e.g., might result in child protection\/apprehension)"},"6":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[6] Used another service altogether (e.g., naturopathy or cultural practices)"},"7":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[7] Unaware of what this service is or it's importance"},"8":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[8] Other ____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a1-q1","id":"q3-a1-q1","answer":"[3] I am waiting to access this service (a referral is in process\/I am on a waiting list)"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Prenatal Education (Prenatal classes for childbirth, breastfeeding, infant care, etc.)","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Have you accessed or tried to access this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1","acount":3,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1","answer":"[1] I have accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a2-q1-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1","answer":"[2] I have not accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Did you try to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you tried to access this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Please indicate the types of barriers that prevented you from accessing\r\nthis service? (If more than one, please list all)\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{1} Service not offered at a convenient time (e.g., during ?business? hours only)"},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{2} Service not offered at a convenient location (e.g., across town or out of town)"},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{3} Did not have the resources to travel to the service (e.g., no bus or taxi fare)"},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{4} Found the other costs to get there too high (e.g. time off work\/school)"},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{5} Health problems interfered (e.g. physical or mental health problems including substances)"},"6":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{6} Family problems interfered (e.g. unstable living situation, intimate partner violence)"},"7":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{7} Service not available (e.g., after hours primary healthcare)"},"8":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{8} Other ____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] No","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Please indicate what prevented you from trying to access this service:\r","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Perceived service as unnecessary (e.g., believed the service was not needed)"},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] Perceived service as ineffective (e.g., believed the service did not help)"},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[3] Perceived service as insensitive (e.g., culturally inappropriate)"},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[4] Was ashamed\/embarrassed to seek service (e.g., stigma associated with mental health\/substances)"},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[5] Perceived service as hostile (e.g., might result in child protection\/apprehension)"},"6":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[6] Used another service altogether (e.g., naturopathy or cultural practices)"},"7":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[7] Unaware of what this service is or it's importance"},"8":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[8] Other ____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a2-q1","id":"q3-a2-q1","answer":"[3] I am waiting to access this service (a referral is in process\/I am on a waiting list)"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Family Resource Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q1","id":"q3-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Prenatal\/parenting program for youth (includes school based programming)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q1","id":"q3-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Adoption Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q1","id":"q3-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}First Nations and Aboriginal Support Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a6-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q1","id":"q3-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a6-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Multicultural Support Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a7-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q1","id":"q3-a7-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a7-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q1","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q3","id":"q3-a7-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q1","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q3","id":"q3-a7-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q1","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q3","id":"q3-a7-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q1","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q3","id":"q3-a7-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q1","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q2","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q3","id":"q3-a7-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"8":{"qnum":"q3","id":"PREG","answer":"{#}Other pregnancy related support programs","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q3-a8-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q1","id":"q3-a8-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q3-a8-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q2","id":"q3-a8-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q3-a8-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q1","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q2","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q1","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q2","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q1","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q2","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q1","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q2","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q1","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q2","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q3","id":"q3-a8-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"question":"Mental Health\/Crisis Intervention\r","id":"q4","qnum":"q4","acount":11,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Adult Outpatient Mental Health Clinic (Community Mental Health Team)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q1","id":"q4-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Reproductive Mental Health Services (includes professionally led groups, psychiatry, etc.)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q1","id":"q4-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Child and Youth Mental Health Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q1","id":"q4-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Youth Forensic Psychiatric Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q1","id":"q4-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Community Counseling Services (e.g. Adult or Family Services)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q1","id":"q4-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Crisis Intervention Services (includes Intimate Partner Violence Services)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a6-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q1","id":"q4-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a6-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Primary Care Provider","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a7-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q1","id":"q4-a7-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a7-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a7-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a7-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a7-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a7-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a7-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"8":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Peer Support (e.g. Pacific Postpartum Support Society)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a8-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q1","id":"q4-a8-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a8-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a8-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a8-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a8-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a8-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a8-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"9":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Victim Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a9-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q1","id":"q4-a9-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a9-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a9-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a9-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a9-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a9-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a9-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"10":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Family Support Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a10-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q1","id":"q4-a10-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a10-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q1","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q3","id":"q4-a10-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q1","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q3","id":"q4-a10-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q1","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q3","id":"q4-a10-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q1","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q3","id":"q4-a10-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q1","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q2","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q3","id":"q4-a10-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"11":{"qnum":"q4","id":"q4","answer":"{#}Other mental health (other than substance use programs)","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q4-a11-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q1","id":"q4-a11-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q4-a11-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q2","id":"q4-a11-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q4-a11-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q1","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q2","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q1","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q2","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q1","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q2","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q1","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q2","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q1","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q2","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q3","id":"q4-a11-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"question":"Substance Use and Harm Reduction\r","id":"q5","qnum":"q5","acount":7,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Smoking Cessation Support (e.g. Quit Now)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q1","id":"q5-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Residential Drug Treatment Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q1","id":"q5-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Counseling for Alcohol Use","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q1","id":"q5-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Counseling for Other Substance Use","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q1","id":"q5-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Primary Care Provider","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q1","id":"q5-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Harm reduction\/needle exchange services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a6-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q1","id":"q5-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a6-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q5-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q5-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q5-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q5-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q5-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q5","id":"q5","answer":"{#}Other substance use or harm reduction program","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q5-a7-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q1","id":"q5-a7-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q5-a7-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q2","id":"q5-a7-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q5-a7-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q1","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q2","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q1","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q2","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q1","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q2","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q1","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q2","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q1","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q2","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q3","id":"q5-a7-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"question":"Health Care\r","id":"q6","qnum":"q6","acount":16,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Primary Care Provider (includes Walk-in Clinic)","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1","acount":3,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1","answer":"[1] I have accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Do you know about the 24-hour tele-nursing service (dial 8-1-1) in BC?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q2","answer":"[2] No"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q3","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Primary Care Provider or clinic?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the service?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q6","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q6","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a1-q6","answer":"__ __"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q3","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Primary Care Provider or clinic?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the service?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q6","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q6","id":"q6-a1-q1-a1-q3-a2-q6","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1","answer":"[2] I have not accessed this service","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Did you try to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Yes","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you tried to access this service in the last 4 weeks?\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Please indicate the types of barriers that prevented you from accessing\r\nthis service? (If more than one, please list all)\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{1} Service not offered at a convenient time (e.g., during ?business? hours only)"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{2} Service not offered at a convenient location (e.g., across town or out of town)"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{3} Did not have the resources to travel to the service (e.g., no bus or taxi fare)"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{4} Found the other costs to get there too high (e.g. time off work\/school)"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{5} Health problems interfered (e.g. physical or mental health problems including substances)"},"6":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{6} Family problems interfered (e.g. unstable living situation, intimate partner violence)"},"7":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{7} Service not available (e.g., after hours primary healthcare)"},"8":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a1-q2","answer":"{8} Other ____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] No","context_questions":{"qcount":1,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Please indicate what prevented you from trying to access this service:\r","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","acount":8,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[1] Perceived service as unnecessary (e.g., believed the service was not needed)"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[2] Perceived service as ineffective (e.g., believed the service did not help)"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[3] Perceived service as insensitive (e.g., culturally inappropriate)"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[4] Was ashamed\/embarrassed to seek service (e.g., stigma associated with mental health\/substances)"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[5] Perceived service as hostile (e.g., might result in child protection\/apprehension)"},"6":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[6] Used another service altogether (e.g., naturopathy or cultural practices)"},"7":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[7] Unaware of what this service is or it's importance"},"8":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1-a2-q1-a2-q1","answer":"[8] Other ____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a1-q1","id":"q6-a1-q1","answer":"[3] I am waiting to access this service (a referral is in process\/I am on a waiting list)"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Emergency Room","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q1","id":"q6-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Do you know about the 24-hour tele-nursing service (dial 8-1-1) in BC?\r","id":"q6-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a2-q2","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q2","id":"q6-a2-q2","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q2","id":"q6-a2-q2","answer":"[2] No"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a2-q3","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3","id":"q6-a2-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q1","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q2","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q3","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Emergency Room?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the Emergency Room?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q6","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q6","id":"q6-a2-q3-a1-q6","answer":"__ __"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3","id":"q6-a2-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q1","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q2","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q3","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Primary Care Provider or clinic?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the service?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q6","qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q6","id":"q6-a2-q3-a2-q6","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Hospital","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q1","id":"q6-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a3-q2","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2","id":"q6-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Primary Care Provider or clinic?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the service?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q6","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q6","id":"q6-a3-q2-a1-q6","answer":"__ __"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2","id":"q6-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":6,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"On this occasion, did you access the 24-hour tele-nursing service (8-1-1)\r\nprior to visiting the Primary Care Provider or clinic?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q4","answer":"[2] No"}}},"5":{"question":"On this occasion, who did you see at the service?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","answer":"[1] A doctor"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","answer":"[2] A nurse"},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","answer":"[3] A nurse-practitioner"},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","answer":"[4] An intern\/student"},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q5","answer":"[5] I don't know"}}},"6":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q6","qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q6","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q6","id":"q6-a3-q2-a2-q6","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Public Health and Dental Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q1","id":"q6-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Public Health Audiology Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q1","id":"q6-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Public Health Speech Pathology Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a6-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q1","id":"q6-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a6-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Public Health Other (Nutrition)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a7-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q1","id":"q6-a7-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a7-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a7-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a7-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a7-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a7-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a7-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"8":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Physician Specialist ? including Pediatrician","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a8-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q1","id":"q6-a8-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a8-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a8-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a8-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a8-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a8-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a8-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"9":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}First Nations Community Health Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a9-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q1","id":"q6-a9-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a9-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a9-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a9-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a9-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a9-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a9-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"10":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Breastfeeding Clinic\/Lactation Consultation","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a10-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q1","id":"q6-a10-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a10-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a10-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a10-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a10-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a10-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a10-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"11":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Early Intervention Therapies","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a11-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q1","id":"q6-a11-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a11-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a11-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a11-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a11-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a11-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a11-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"12":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Nursing Support Services (includes At Home Program)","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a12-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q1","id":"q6-a12-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Do you know about the 24-hour tele-nursing service (dial 8-1-1) in BC?\r","id":"q6-a12-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q2","acount":2,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q2","id":"q6-a12-q2","answer":"[1] Yes"},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q2","id":"q6-a12-q2","answer":"[2] No"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a12-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":5,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q1","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q2","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q4","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q4","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q4","answer":"Minutes: __ __"}}},"5":{"question":"Please specify the name of the Nursing Support Service you accessed on this\r\noccasion (excluding the Nurse-Family Partnership):\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q5","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q5","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q5","id":"q6-a12-q3-a1-q5","answer":"Name: ____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":5,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q1","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q2","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q4","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q4","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q4","answer":"Minutes: __ __"}}},"5":{"question":"Please specify the name of the Nursing Support Service you accessed on this\r\noccasion (excluding the Nurse-Family Partnership):\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q5","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q5","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q5","id":"q6-a12-q3-a2-q5","answer":"Name: ____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":5,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q1","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q2","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q4","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q4","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q4","answer":"Minutes: __ __"}}},"5":{"question":"Please specify the name of the Nursing Support Service you accessed on this\r\noccasion (excluding the Nurse-Family Partnership):\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q5","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q5","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q5","id":"q6-a12-q3-a3-q5","answer":"Name: ____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":5,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q1","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q2","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q4","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q4","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q4","answer":"Minutes: __ __"}}},"5":{"question":"Please specify the name of the Nursing Support Service you accessed on this\r\noccasion (excluding the Nurse-Family Partnership):\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q5","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q5","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q5","id":"q6-a12-q3-a4-q5","answer":"Name: ____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":5,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q1","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q2","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q3","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}},"4":{"question":"How long did accessing this service take (in minutes)?\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q4","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q4","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q4","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q4","answer":"Minutes: __ __"}}},"5":{"question":"Please specify the name of the Nursing Support Service you accessed on this\r\noccasion (excluding the Nurse-Family Partnership):\r","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q5","qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q5","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q5","id":"q6-a12-q3-a5-q5","answer":"Name: ____"}}}}}}}}}}},"13":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}STI Clinic","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a13-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q1","id":"q6-a13-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a13-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a13-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a13-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a13-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a13-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a13-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"14":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Youth Clinic (includes Sexual Health Clinic, Options, etc)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a14-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q1","id":"q6-a14-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a14-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a14-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a14-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a14-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a14-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a14-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"15":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Hospital Ambulatory Care Centre","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a15-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q1","id":"q6-a15-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a15-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q1","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q3","id":"q6-a15-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q1","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q3","id":"q6-a15-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q1","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q3","id":"q6-a15-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q1","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q3","id":"q6-a15-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q1","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q2","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q3","id":"q6-a15-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"16":{"qnum":"q6","id":"q6","answer":"{#}Other health care","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q6-a16-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q1","id":"q6-a16-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q6-a16-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q2","id":"q6-a16-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q6-a16-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q1","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q2","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q1","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q2","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q1","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q2","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q1","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q2","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q1","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q2","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q3","id":"q6-a16-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"question":"Children's Services\r","id":"q7","qnum":"q7","acount":6,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Infant's Development Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q1","id":"q7-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q7-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q7-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q7-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q7-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q7-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Aboriginal Infant Development Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q1","id":"q7-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q7-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q7-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q7-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q7-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q7-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Supported Child Development","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q1","id":"q7-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q7-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q7-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q7-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q7-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q7-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Aboriginal Supported Child Development","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q1","id":"q7-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q7-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q7-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q7-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q7-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q7-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Child Care Resource and Referral","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q1","id":"q7-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q7-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q7-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q7-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q7-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q7-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q7","id":"q7","answer":"{#}Other: Please specify:","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q7-a6-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q1","id":"q7-a6-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q7-a6-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q2","id":"q7-a6-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q7-a6-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q1","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q2","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q1","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q2","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q1","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q2","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q1","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q2","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q1","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q2","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q3","id":"q7-a6-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"8":{"question":"Shelter and Housing\r","id":"q8","qnum":"q8","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8","id":"q8","answer":"{#}Emergency Shelter","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q8-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q1","id":"q8-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q8-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q8-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q8-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q8-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q8-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q8-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8","id":"q8","answer":"{#}Women's Transition Housing\/Shelter","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q8-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q1","id":"q8-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q8-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q8-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q8-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q8-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q8-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q8-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8","id":"q8","answer":"{#}Supportive Housing (includes Maternity Home)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q8-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q1","id":"q8-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q8-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q8-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q8-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q8-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q8-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q8-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8","id":"q8","answer":"{#}Subsidized Housing","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q8-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q1","id":"q8-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q8-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q8-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q8-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q8-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q8-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q8-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8","id":"q8","answer":"{#}Other: Please specify:","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q8-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q1","id":"q8-a5-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q8-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q2","id":"q8-a5-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q8-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q1","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q2","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q1","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q2","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q1","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q2","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q1","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q2","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q1","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q2","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q3","id":"q8-a5-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"9":{"question":"Education and Employment\r","id":"q9","qnum":"q9","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9","id":"q9","answer":"{#}Adult Graduation Diploma Program","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q9-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q1","id":"q9-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q9-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q9-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q9-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q9-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q9-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q9-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9","id":"q9","answer":"{#}General Education Development Testing Service","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q9-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q1","id":"q9-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q9-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q9-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q9-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q9-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q9-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q9-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9","id":"q9","answer":"{#}School District Support Programs","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q9-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q1","id":"q9-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q9-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q9-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q9-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q9-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q9-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q9-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9","id":"q9","answer":"{#}Job, Career and\/or Apprenticeship Programs","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q9-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q1","id":"q9-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q9-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q9-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q9-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q9-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q9-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q9-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9","id":"q9","answer":"{#}Life Skills","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q9-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q1","id":"q9-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q9-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q9-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q9-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q9-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q9-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q9-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}},"10":{"question":"Other Community Programs and Services\r","id":"q10","qnum":"q10","acount":7,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Charitable Services (food bank, clothing, furniture, toys, etc.)","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q1","id":"q10-a1-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a1-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a1-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a1-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a1-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a1-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Legal Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q1","id":"q10-a2-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a2-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a2-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a2-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a2-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a2-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Immigrant and Refugee Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q1","id":"q10-a3-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a3-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a3-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a3-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a3-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a3-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}DNA Paternity Testing","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q1","id":"q10-a4-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a4-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a4-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a4-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a4-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a4-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Probation Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q1","id":"q10-a5-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a5-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a5-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a5-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a5-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a5-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"6":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Youth or Adult Custody Services","context_questions":{"qcount":2,"questions":{"1":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a6-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q1","id":"q10-a6-q1","answer":"1~28"}}},"2":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a6-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q1","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q3","id":"q10-a6-q2-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q1","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q3","id":"q10-a6-q2-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q1","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q3","id":"q10-a6-q2-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q1","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q3","id":"q10-a6-q2-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q1","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q2","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q3","id":"q10-a6-q2-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}},"7":{"qnum":"q10","id":"q10","answer":"{#}Other: Please specify:","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"Name of service:\r","id":"q10-a7-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q1","id":"q10-a7-q1","answer":"____"}}},"2":{"question":"How many times have you accessed this service in the last 4 weeks? \r\nIf more than once [goto PREG].\r","id":"q10-a7-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q2","id":"q10-a7-q2","answer":"1~28"}}},"3":{"question":"Describe the last few times you used this service\r","id":"q10-a7-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3","acount":5,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3","answer":"{first} first service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the first service use?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q1","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q2","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3-a1-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"2":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3","answer":"{second} second service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the second service use?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q1","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q2","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3-a2-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"3":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3","answer":"{third} third service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the third service use?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q1","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q2","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3-a3-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"4":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3","answer":"{fourth} fourth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fourth service use?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q1","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q2","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3-a4-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}},"5":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3","answer":"{fifth} fifth service use?","context_questions":{"qcount":3,"questions":{"1":{"question":"What was the approximate date of the fifth service use?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q1","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q1","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q1","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q1","answer":"y\/m\/d"}}},"2":{"question":"In total, what did it cost you to access this service?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q2","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q2","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q2","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q2","answer":"__ __"}}},"3":{"question":"On this occasion, what were the reasons for this cost?\r","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q3","qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q3","acount":1,"answers":{"1":{"qnum":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q3","id":"q10-a7-q3-a5-q3","answer":"____"}}}}}}}}}}}}}}};
